Jackie Martin Papers
Jackie Martin Papers
- Negatives and contacts
  - Assorted negatives, 1935-1965
    - Crittendon home babies (Box 32)
    - Government girls series; Alma Siuox Searberry (Box 32)
    - Pirates den (Box 32)
    - Ruth Draper; Mildred Pepper, Wife of Senator; Irene Caldwell; Ruth Draper, Hazel Vandenburg, Mrs. Ham Fish, Lady Lewis (Box 32)
    - Sally Evans at piano (Box 32)
    - Ned Brunson Harris (Box 32)
    - Bakery shop (Box 32)
    - Mrs. Jules C. Risher Westchester (Box 32)
    - Jeanne d'Arc/World War I/Horse and IT Myer (Box 32)
    - Helen Koues, Editor of Good Housekeeping at Dupont Circle (Box 32)
    - Little Clima dog on piano keyboard (Box 32)
    - Fan and bills (Box 32)
    - Embassy diary (Box 32)
    - Bea Lillie and Earl Carroll (Box 32)
    - Swa's party (Box 32)
    - Walter Howey and Arthur Brisbane at 15 Dupont Circle, original a 35mm #2 (Box 32)
    - Me and gang at Times-Herald office with boss (Box 32)
    - Boss, Carol French, and I leaving by plane for Atlanta (Box 32)
    - Jackson's Hole, Wyoming; Henry and Rose Crabtree (Box 32)
    - Mrs. Shelton's party (Box 32)
    - Birthday Party held for Eleanor Patterson by girls at the office (Box 32)
    - Mrs. Patterson, Tom White, Bill Bullitt (Box 32)
    - Boss in composing room and copy negs (Box 32)
    - Birthday cake (May 7) at Times-Herald; Cissy Patterson and Co. (Box 32)
    - Shadow Cross tour, St. Patrick's Altar, See also Negatives and contacts: Assorted negatives 1935-1965: Churches: Cathedral, Lutheran-South Circle (Box 32)
    - Gold Plate supper; Evalyn McLean and kids; Roosevelt's kids, See also Negatives and contacts: Assorted negatives 1935-1965: White House and Negatives and contacts: Biographical negatives: Jackie Martin shoots Evalyn McLean's table... (Box 32)
    - Mrs. Richard Casey (Mai) cocktail party; press; Mrs. Robert LeBaron, See also Negatives and contacts: Biographical negatives: Jackie Martin at party for Mai Casey at Willard (Box 32)
    - Hozen dinner; "Jeremp" and Mary Randolph, 28 Jun 1939 (Box 32)
    - Testimonial dinner for Commissioner Hozen; Evie Robert and Norren Delano Roosevelt (Box 32)
    - Gold Cup race; Liz Whitney and FDR Jr., See also Negatives and contacts: Newspaper negatives 1939-1948: Warrenton VA Gold Cup Race (Box 32)
    - Senator Johnson, Colorado, for News-Week; See also Negatives and contacts: Assorted negatives 1935-1965: Inside Capitol (Box 32)
    - President, Mrs. Truman, and Margaret (ANWC event) and Margaret Hart Cowley; Genevieve Reynolds Eastham, See also Negatives and contacts: Assorted negatives 1935-1965: Batts, Tydings; A.N.W.C. party; Truman (Box 32)
    - Margaret Truman, Mme. Gromyko, and Adm. Vardainaur, See also Negative and contacts: Assorted negatives 1935-1965: Valentine Ball (Truman); Statler; Gromyko (Box 32)
    - Roosevelt at a meeting at 15 Dupont Circle (Box 32)
    - Opening of self-help exchange; Mrs. Roosevelt now (Box 32)
    - Soviet Embassy party for Geno Herrick (Box 32)
    - Mrs. Robert LeBaron (Box 32)
    - Mme. Saita's Party, Japanese Embassy, K Street (Box 32)
    - Chicago Sun at Washington Bureau; Fields, Trumans, and Evans; L to R: Mr. Silliman Evans (Publisher of C-S); Mr.Bascom X. Timmons (Managing Editor); Mr. Marshall Fields (Owner of C-S) (Box 32)
    - Vaille Vante, See Negatives and contacts: Assorted negatives: 1935-1965: Supreme Court
    - Jeeateer House, See Negatives and contacts: Assorted negatives 1935-1965: Street scenes and private houses
    - Handy Studio Pix; Mrs. Evans and Mrs. Cox, See Negatives and contacts: Assorted negatives 1935-1965: Library of Congress and Folger
    - Mrs. Patterson; Stokowski, Dr. Guin, and Youth Orchestra (Box 32)
    - Race: War Admiral and Sea Biscuit, Horse Race (Box 32)
    - Mexican Embassy party (Box 32)
    - Girl model in shower, 15 Dupont Circle (Box 32)
    - Gold Plate dinner 1939; Evalyn McLean, Maurice Stars, Roosevelts, See also Negatives and contacts: Assorted negatives 1935-1965: White House and Negatives and contacts: Biographical negatives: Jackie Martin shoots Evalyn McLean's table... (Box 32)
    - Cuban Embassy party (Box 32)
    - Drucie Snyder story; reception-secretary and Mrs. Snyder; secretary and Dean Redreson, and Mrs. Bevin (Box 32)
    - Sarah Churchill and Olway Ian (Box 32)
    - Press Cup regatta (Box 32)
    - Stanley Woodward, See Negatives and contacts: Assorted negatives 1935-1965: State Department and Negatives and contacts: Assorted negatives 1935-1965: White House
    - Jackie Martin and photo branch stuff; Gane Lazarre, Paris; off for 1st home leave, 01 May 1952 (Box 32)
    - Prints: Staff shot, Easter 1954; 5 Gabriel (Box 32)
    - Antiques at 525 Wagram (Box 32)
    - The Green Minx in Paris, 1953 (Box 32)
    - Antiques at 525 the Wagram (Box 32)
    - Antiques at 525 the Wagram Hotel, April 1954; Braun Hotsry Stobolite (Box 32)
    - Antiques at 525 the Wagram (Box 32)
    - Apartment Wagram, the Tuileries 524-525 (Box 32)
    - Night Shot From the Wagram (Box 32)
    - Shots from the Wagram (Box 32)
    - Wagram Hotel - Joan of Arc Day Parade, 09 May 1954? (Box 32)
    - Inauguration January, Washington D.C., 1953 (Box 32)
    - SHAPE, Pervianent and NAT Repo, 26 Feb 1953 (Box 32)
    - NATO Council Meets in Paris, 23 Apr 1953 (Box 32)
    - Brussels Conference I, December 1950 (Box 32)
    - Brussels Conference II, SHAPE Headquarters opened, 23 Jul 1951; Marley, 35mm #1 (Box 32)
    - SHAPE Headquarters opened, 23 Jul 1951; Marley, 35mm #2 (Box 32)
    - SHAPE Headquarters opened, 23 Jul 1951; Marley, 35mm #3 (Box 32)
    - PAR 3035-3039A (Box 32)
    - Ambassador Fred L. Anderson; MSA-SRE, August 1953 (Box 32)
    - Press Party Brussels; USIS-ECA Hager-Madden-Ambassador Murphy, 1951? (Box 32)
    - Crucifix between Brussels and Paris, Winter 1952 (Box 32)
    - Crossing over Switzerland between Rome and Paris, 18 Apr 1953 (Box 32)
    - Capri from air, 1953 (Box 32)
    - Trip Belgrade-Graz, 1952; Joh and Virginia McGovern; Paul and Betty Shinkmann and Boy; Yugo-Austrian Border and Customs Men (Yugo Side), Graz, Austria (Box 32)
    - Between Yugo and Greece Borders and Athens Train, 1953 (Box 32)
    - Istanbul and Ankara, seconds (Box 32)
    - MOR 3 (Box 32)
    - Tuilieries parade, the Wagram (Box 32)
    - Parades past Wagram, Tuilieries (Box 32)
    - Roven Easter by myself and Green Minx, 19 Apr 1954 (Box 32)
    - Cologne, 10 Apr 1954-11 Apr 1954 (Box 32)
    - Chartres Cathedral, 1953 (Box 32)
    - Clare and Henry Luce at San Remo, Italy; and Nice, France, August 1953 (Box 32)
    - 5 ambasadors all in Paris: Dunn, Draper, Anderson, Merchant, Edwards; Hotel Scrilie, 1952 (Box 32)
    - Reception: Inter-Allie Circle, 1951; Ambassadors Katz, Foster, Wood; ECA, ADM, Washington, Draper and Acheson, 31 Oct 1952; Ray P. Ladden, Robert Barnes, Wiliam Koren, Jr; Awards (Box 32)
    - Ambassadors Harriman and Draper (Box 32)
    - Waldemar Nielsen leaves Paris - director of information NSA/SRE (Box 32)
    - Greece: Athens Airport, 08 Apr 1953; Probably Athens from air (Box 32)
    - Greece: Byzantine Church at Dafin in Athens, 1953 (Box 32)
    - Greece contacts, Chicago Sun (Box 33)
    - Greece: Roman Temple to Zeus, 1953 (Box 33)
    - Greece: the Parthenon and the Aesopohio, 1953 (Box 33)
    - Greece: Athens air views, 1953 (Box 33)
    - Montreux, Switzerland, 1952 (Box 33)
    - Rein Falls, Switzerland, July-August 1951 (Box 33)
    - Lichtenstein summer vacation, Jul 1951-Aug 1951 (Box 33)
    - Greece, Elensis, 1953 (Box 33)
    - Helen Kirkpatrick, Farewell party at Henry Parkivon's and Smith GRAD group in Paris (Box 33)
    - The Louvre and Tuillieries, from Wagram Hotel, 11 Nov 1952 (Box 33)
    - American Military Cemetary at Surenes; Generals Marshall, Ridgeway, Juin; Perle Mesta, Tony Biddle (Box 33)
    - Eiffel Tower and Searchlight "V" at NIght from 525 Wagram (Box 33)
    - Paris; Louvre from Wagram fireworks shot, 14 Jul (Box 33)
    - Party at USIS for India Edwards and Mydna Loy; 41 Fauberg St, Honore, 1952 (Box 33)
    - Seaborn-Foster wedding, 1931; contacts only (Box 33)
    - Mrs. Averill Harriman, Paris, 1951 (Box 33)
    - Chantilly picnic; Roscoe and Charlotte Drummond, Jane, Spring 1951 (Box 33)
    - Fontaine Bleu with Frances Hughes and husband, 1953 (Box 33)
    - Between Gander and NYC, 04 Dec 1953-05 Dec 1953 (Box 33)
    - Ike and Joe Collins at Orly, 1952 (Box 33)
    - Sustin; Paris; Switzerland; Montreux (Box 33)
    - Calendars, 1950-1954 (Box 33)
    - Ankara, Turkey, 09 Apr 1953-18 Apr 1953; good shots (Box 33)
    - Istanbul, Turkey, 09 Apr 1953-18 Apr 1953; good shots (Box 33)
    - Perle Mesta, American minister to Luxembourg, 1953 (Box 33)
    - Perle Mesta; party at residence for U.S. soldiers, 1953 (Box 33)
    - Mrs. Roosevelt at American Women's Club, Paris; Mrs. Eisenhower, Mrs. Pleven, Mrs. Druce, Mrs. Warren Austin, 12 Nov 1951 (Box 33)
    - General Eisenhower arrives in Paris to form SHAPE, Jan 1951 (Box 33)
    - Herbert Marshall (Box 33)
    - Frances Del, Joel McRol (Box 33)
    - Pat O'Brien (Box 33)
    - Joan Blondell, Dick Powell (Box 33)
    - Rosalind Russell (Box 33)
    - Edward G. Robinson (Box 33)
    - Louise Rainer (Box 33)
    - Saie Sendegard (Box 33)
    - Rosalie Stewart, Frances Marion (Box 33)
    - Bette Davis (Box 33)
    - Gene Raymond (Box 33)
    - Rosalie Stweart, Hollywood (Box 33)
    - Anna Sten (Box 33)
    - Helen Ferguson, Fred Perry (Box 33)
    - Tyrone Power (Box 33)
    - Gypsy Rose Lee, 1939-1940; Striptease at French Benefit, Ritz Carlton (Box 33)
    - Burns and Allen (Box 33)
    - Hollywood shots including Jackie Martin (Box 33)
    - Ona Nelson, "Steve's" (Box 33)
    - Powell, Zarina, Gambey (Box 33)
    - George Raft (Box 33)
    - Jane Withers (Box 33)
    - Jackie; Olney Theater; Helen Twelvetrees, Karen Morley (Box 33)
    - Walter Abel, Marietta Bitters (Box 33)
    - Anita Louise (Box 33)
    - Ed Bergen (Box 33)
    - Fannie Brice - Sophie Tucker (Box 33)
    - Fashion (Box 33)
    - Errol Flynn (Box 33)
    - Preston Foster (Box 33)
    - Helen Ferguson (Box 33)
    - Bea Lillie, Fannie Brice (Box 33)
    - Carole Lombard (Box 33)
    - L.J. Gibbens (Box 33)
    - Walter Huston (Box 33)
    - Irene, designer (Box 33)
    - Patsy Kelly (Box 33)
    - Irene Dunne (Box 33)
    - Maxine Doyle (Box 33)
    - Nelson Eddy (Box 33)
    - Dorothy Arzner (Box 33)
    - Fred Bartholomew (Box 33)
    - Billie Burke (Box 33)
    - Wendy Barrie (Box 33)
    - Constance Bennett (Box 33)
    - Claudette Colber (Box 33)
    - Joan Crawford (missing as of 04/23/09)
    - Opening of "Hurricane" (Box 33)
    - Shirley Temple (Box 33)
    - Spencer Tracy (Box 33)
    - Coward and Bea Lillie (Box 33)
    - Louela Parsons; husband, Dr. Martin and group (Box 33)
    - Mary Pickford, Betty Hines, Andy Kelly (Box 33)
    - Farm and Home contacts (Box 33)
    - Farm and Home, Country Gentleman (Box 33)
    - "Climax Blethen" Frederick, Md.; Saturday Evening Post (Box 33)
    - Blethen of Frederick, Md; baseball (Box 33)
    - LOCH; Ladies Home Journal, contacts (Box 33)
    - Dower House, contacts (Box 33)
    - "No Apples This Time" Ladies Home Journal (Box 33)
    - Tyson, Betty; Newport (Box 34)
    - Tyson Barbeque; Eleanor Patterson (Box 34)
    - Press Part, Perle Mesta, Jul 1949 (Box 34)
    - Betty Tyson, Newport (Box 34)
    - Mesta reception after premiere of "Search", 27 Apr 1948 (Box 34)
    - Mesta Party for Women Broadcasters, Radio Gals, 31 Jan 1948 (Box 34)
    - Marguerite Skriven Layth (Box 34)
    - Perle Mesta, miscellaneous (Box 34)
    - Mrs. George Mesta Party, 09 Feb 1946 (Box 34)
    - Army Nurses for Madamoiselle; Col Flikke (Box 34)
    - McAfee; WAVES (Box 34)
    - General Jacob L. Devers, helicopter (Box 34)
    - Blair House (Box 34)
    - DeSeversky and Koop (Box 34)
    - Soviet Embassy; Novikov; N. Burden and Mme. Novikov, 09 Apr 1944 (Box 34)
    - Flying Nurses; Bowman Field, KY (Box 34)
    - Syracuse University, Arents Award; Chancellor and Mrs. Graham, Hughes, Delta Gamma House (Box 34)
    - Nag's Head vacation, 1946? (Box 34)
    - Syracuse University (Box 34)
    - Truman addresses 81st Congress, 05 Jan 1949 (Box 34)
    - Bertha Joseph and Senator Radcliff at Senate O.B. (Box 34)
    - Inaugural parade, 20 Jan 1949 (Box 34)
    - Blair House, 1946 (Box 34)
    - Newspaper Womens Club Party at Mayflower, 1947; Truman, Hart, Canby (Box 34)
    - Pughs and Clements (Box 34)
    - Hazel Vandenburg; Clare Luce and Jackie Martin (Box 34)
    - USSH officials and Mrs. Roosevelt (Box 34)
    - Embassy families; Paternottes, Belgium; Bonnets, France (Box 34)
    - Roosevelt's fireside chat, 23 Feb 1942 (Box 34)
    - President's birthday ball; Eleanor Roosevelt, Jean Harlow, Robert Taylor (Box 34)
    - White House, contacts (Box 34)
    - White House, 1948; Steve Early, Press, Myrtle Bergheim, Jerry (Box 34)
    - Clare Luce; Washington apartment (Wardman Park Annex); Mrs. Dwight Davis (Box 34)
    - Don Cossacks; Trumans; Washington, Mar 1948 (Box 34)
    - Mesta Party, Democratic Convention, 13 Jul 1948 (Box 34)
    - Companion Reader editors in Washington (Box 34)
    - Helen Woods - Randy Burgess Wedding (Box 34)
    - Eustis - Blake (Box 34)
    - Gourmets, Statler Hotel, 21 Jun 1949 (Box 34)
    - "Hot Money" Ladies Home Journal (Box 34)
    - Grocery manufacturers, 31 Jan 1948 (Box 34)
    - Washington: City of Destiny, negatives for book made with Frank Waldrop (Box 35)
    - Aerosol Bomb Country Gentleman (Box 36)
    - Al Bennett at airport, N.J. Madamoiselle (Box 36)
    - Fort Benning, 03 Nov 1949-05 Nov 1949 (Box 36)
    - Triplets, Doctor's Hospital (Box 36)
    - Disastrous Hobby-Knox party, negatives out of focus (Box 36)
    - Foreign Service Girls Parade, 01 Oct 1949 (Box 36)
    - Capt. Frederick J. Bell and family Ladies Home Journal (Box 36)
    - Greta Kempton's portraits (Box 36)
    - A.B.C. Steel Equipment Co. (Box 36)
    - Valentine Ball (Truman); Statler; Gromyko, 14 Feb 1949 (Box 36)
    - Chemical farming, Coral Gables (Box 36)
    - Luftwaif N.Y. Mirror, Jul 1947 (Box 36)
    - Major General Levin Campbell, Jr., Lt. Col. Herbert White (Box 36)
    - Nell Nichols Womans Home Companion (Box 36)
    - William Jeffers (Box 36)
    - Death Drivers (Box 36)
    - Special party for Tom Wrigley at Carlton Hotel; President's birthday ball (Box 36)
    - Reader Editors Woman's Home Companion, Mar 1942 (Box 36)
    - Capt. Sue Dauser, head of Navy nurses (Box 36)
    - David Berger (Box 36)
    - Greta Kempton, artist at Corcoran, 05 Feb 1949 (Box 36)
    - Henrietta Swope American Weekly (Box 36)
    - "Terry" for Terry Wrigley, James Carey and Wiliam Green, 1948 (Box 36)
    - Occidental Restaurant, 1947 (Box 36)
    - Private Brady E. Ferguson McCall's (Box 36)
    - Mrs. Dwight Davis party; Hobby; A. Rogers (Box 36)
    - First Aid, Shoreham Hotel; Mrs. Goodwin's class Town and Country (Box 36)
    - The Ellis Maple family, Plymouth, N.C. (Box 36)
    - Major Julia Flikke, head of Army Nurse Corp Woman's Home Companion (Box 36)
    - Phillipine women (Box 36)
    - Washington Canteen Town and Country (Box 36)
    - Norman Corwin and Rear Adm. Victory Maritime Commission (Box 36)
    - Mary Clark's mother and sister (Box 36)
    - Trailortown Woman's Home Companion (Box 36)
    - V-Mail (Box 36)
    - American Legion Boy's Forum (Box 36)
    - Little Bull at the USSH farm (Box 36)
    - Liz Churchill's party for the Biffles, Club of All Nations, Mar 1949 (Box 36)
    - Chavez wedding reception, Shoreham, 09 Feb 1946 (Box 36)
    - Lazzari N.Y. Mirror, Jul 1947 (Box 36)
    - Francis Craig "Near You", Dec 1947 (Box 36)
    - "D.C. Melody" stage; Ethel Barrymore (Box 36)
    - Mary Anderson, Women's Bureau (Box 36)
    - Forrest Davis, Cajigas; Chief Justice, Puerto Rico (Box 36)
    - British Benefit, Anderson House (Box 36)
    - Azizia Newman (Box 36)
    - "D.C. Melody," Ethel Barrymore, rehearsal (Box 36)
    - Dr. Richards, Johns Hopkins Cosmopolitan (Box 36)
    - Dr. Katherine McFarlane, Philadelphia Cosmopolitan (Box 36)
    - Dr. Patricia Draint, Philadelphia Cosmopolitan (Box 36)
    - Peggy the Pony N.Y. Mirror, Jul 1947 (Box 36)
    - Girls at Gayety Theater (Box 37)
    - Hilles Ladies Home Journal (Box 37)
    - Polish Ladies Home Journal (Box 37)
    - Carol Frink (Box 37)
    - White House Spanish class at store (Box 37)
    - Holtsville, Alabama, school kids Country Gentleman (Box 37)
    - Stephens College Tour LOOK (7); Ann Sorency; Dr. Wood Ladies Home Journal (Box 37)
    - Ruth Mitchell and Maj. Carter Glass Jr.; Peg Gossett, NYC (Box 37)
    - Strawbridge, Doeller, dogs (Box 37)
    - Bowling-Sims and Broncho; Catherine Quigley Woman's Home Companion (Box 37)
    - Mr. and Mrs. Hausworth, Ritz Carlton (Box 37)
    - Mabel Walker Willebran (Box 37)
    - Maxine Davis (Box 37)
    - Paul McNutt (Box 37)
    - Daisy Harriman and Maxine Davis (Box 37)
    - Mrs. Lawrence Townsend; Melchoirs old furniture; Princess Colonial; Musical LIFE (Box 37)
    - Rep. and Mrs. Monroney Town and Country (Box 37)
    - Donald Nelson, Saturday Evening Post (Box 37)
    - Navy Department Shots; Nelson, Saturday Evening Post (Box 37)
    - Congressional Group; Reps. Jerry Voorkees, Woodrum; Seantors McNary, Ausitn, Norris, Gillette; Budget Director Harold Smith and G. Watson; Col. Starling Woman's Home Companion (Box 37)
    - Milo Perkins Collier's, This Week (Box 37)
    - Opening of Laurel Race Track (Box 37)
    - Rollie, 1949? (Box 37)
    - International Chidren's Broadcast, Statler (Box 37)
    - Merry Hull, Ohio State University (Box 37)
    - Mary Mundt This Week, Nov 1945 (Box 37)
    - Curley Byrd, Maryland University Saturday Evening Post (Box 37)
    - Senator Joe Ball and family Collier's (Box 37)
    - General and Mrs. Watson (Box 37)
    - Floyd Odlum and Jackie Cochran, Governor Green (Illinois), Don Wilson, Chuck Kerwood and wife; and Joe Edgerton (Box 37)
    - Harold Smith, Director of American Budget (Box 38)
    - Eunice Kennedy and Fay Bentley, Tom Clark American Weekly (Box 38)
    - Prince Carl Gustav, Stockholm (Box 38)
    - Tom Wrigley, Rep. Margaret Chase Smith, Harold Dumont (Box 38)
    - Onan Thornton (Box 38)
    - Muna Lee, Jackie Cochran, Nancy MacClennan (Box 38)
    - Irene Caldwell and Al Warner, birthday party, Mar 1947 (Box 38)
    - White House; Dr. Streetman, Miss Price (Box 38)
    - Sir Wilmot and Lady Lewis; Lord Lothian (Box 38)
    - Chinese Benefit Bazaar, Anne Archibald, Anne Morgan (Box 38)
    - Batts, Tydings; A.N.W.C. party; Truman (Box 38)
    - Pan American Fiesta Woman's Home Companion (Box 38)
    - Irene Junos, mother's birthday party, 21 Oct 1942 (Box 38)
    - Cafritz Party, Foxhall; Christmas season, 1945-1946 (Box 38)
    - Ollie Atkins, W.H.N.P.A. (Box 38)
    - Baron; Silvercruys; Jonathan Daniels and family Town and Country (Box 38)
    - Craig McGeachy (Box 38)
    - Birthday party for Pat Harrison, Carlton Hotel (Box 38)
    - Shouse's Christmas Party (Box 38)
    - Mlle. Maria DiBanco; Mrs. Alan Kirk and Mrs. Phyllis Wright (Box 38)
    - Womens's National Press Club Stunt Awards Dinner, Mayflower, 19 Apr 1947 (Box 38)
    - Meyer's dinner party that followed stunt party, 03 Mar 1948 (Box 38)
    - Newspaper Women's Club Rosemary Ball, 28 May 1946 (Box 38)
    - Cowan-Hager Inaugural Lunch, Statler Hotel; Sec. George Marshall, 01 Jul 1947 (Box 38)
    - 1940 Press Club stunt party (Box 38)
    - Senator and Mrs. Jimmy Byrnes (Box 38)
    - Fashion Show at Statler; Mrs. Truman (Box 38)
    - Town and Country Room (Box 38)
    - Town and Country: Harris, Dewey, R.G. Swing; Mrs. Derek Hoyer-Millar, Mrs. Patrick Hill, Mrs. Tydings, Robert Scotters (Box 38)
    - Electra Waggoner Biggs, J. Walter Thompson (Box 38)
    - Pepperidge Farm, Conn.; Alice Hughes and Gus Sommersburg (Box 38)
    - Alice Hughes and boss, Slotkin (Box 38)
    - Mrs. Chester Davis, Mary P. Routs?, Helen Essary (Box 38)
    - National Women's Press Club Party, Mayflower, 09 Feb 1946 (Box 38)
    - Hager wins Avon Award (Box 38)
    - Christmas party at Alice Brussels (Box 38)
    - Alice's children; Carol Helen and kids (Box 38)
    - Grace Eustis-Phillips wedding, 07 Jan 1949 (Box 38)
    - Punka Holmes wedding (Box 38)
    - Madelaine Loughry's wedding, 1947 (Box 38)
    - John Hull wedding (Box 38)
    - Caldwell-Brombeck wedding; Barbara Caldwell, Sep 1947 (Box 38)
    - Taber baby christening (Box 38)
    - Goldsborough-Moore Wedding, 22 May 1948 (Box 39)
    - Patterson-Simonds, Bellevue-Warrenton, 05 Jun 1948 (Box 39)
    - Early-Elam wedding; Steve Early, Sec. Louis Johnson, Paul Porter (Box 39)
    - Woods-Hollingsworth wedding; Mrs. Arthur Woods (Box 39)
    - Rediken-Halim wedding (Box 39)
    - Defense: Andrews Fidd and General Keussy?; General Bradley and staff; Adam Denfield and Radford (Box 39)
    - Tomb of the Unknown (Box 39)
    - Lincoln Memorial/Watergate concert (Box 39)
    - Government Printing Office; Bureau of Engraving and Printing (Box 39)
    - Archives (Box 39)
    - People (Box 39)
    - Cherry Blossoms, 15 Apr 1947 (Box 39)
    - Cherry Blossoms; Monument; Jefferson Memorial, 1948 (Box 39)
    - Easter at Friendship, 1946 (Box 39)
    - Evalyn McLean's New Year's Eve party, 1945-1946 (Box 39)
    - McLean's party at Friendship for Grace Moore, 1945 (Box 39)
    - Friendship, New Year's Eve, 1945 (Box 39)
    - McLean's press party, 1946 (Box 39)
    - Misc. Washington buildings: Union Station; apt houses on 159th near park; Press Building doorway (Box 39)
    - Zoo sightseeing bus; taxis (Box 39)
    - Mt. Vernon National Airport (Box 39)
    - Independent Agencies: Civil Service, Federal Security, Vets Administration (Box 39)
    - Drucie Snyder; May 1949; 30 Rockefeller Plaza; 13 Apr 1949 (Box 39)
    - Mall buildings; Constitution Ave. buildings: Smithsonian, National Gallery, National Research Institute, Federal Reserve, Atomic Energy Commission (Box 39)
    - Organizations: Pan-American, D.A.R., Red Cross, University Club, Brookings Institution, Scottish Temple, National Education Association, Carnegie Institute, CIO-AF of L (Box 39)
    - Hospitals: Moral Hospital, Biltrender, Moral Research Institute, George Washington University Hospital (Box 39)
    - Stautues and parks: Jackson-LaFayette Park, Scott Circle Underpass, Thomas Circle Underpass; Sheridan Circle; Washington Circle; Grant (Capitol) Circle; Sherman Circle; Asbury Circle; Martin Luther Circle; Apex Bldg; Peace (Capitol); Merchant Marine (Box 39)
    - Churches: Cathedral, Lutheran-South Circle (Box 39)
    - Universities: Howard University, Catholic University (Box 39)
    - Washington Bldgs, unmarked contacts, no negatives (Box 39)
    - Street scenes and private houses (Box 40)
    - School-boy patrol, Parade, Monument-Sylvan Theater (Box 40)
    - Betty Tyson, contacts only (Box 40)
    - State Department; Mme. Ambassador Anderson (Box 40)
    - Eleanor Patterson; Port Washington; LOOK office decorations by Polish Government (Box 40)
    - Library of Congress and Folger (Box 40)
    - Supreme Court (Box 40)
    - Capitol, contacts only (Box 40)
    - Capitol inauguration ceremony from Library Dome, 20 Jan 1949 (Box 40)
    - Capitol ( City of Destiny) fountain, 1948 (Box 40)
    - Capitol from Library of Congress; day and night; Grant Memorial (Box 40)
    - Mrs. Joe E. Davies Tea for Rise Stevens, 10 Mar 1946 (Box 40)
    - Davies' Inaugural Governor's reception "Sea Cloud", 19 Jan 1949 (Box 40)
    - Davies' farewell party for Lord and Lady Halifax, 1946 (Box 40)
    - Evie and Chip Robert; dogs and baby (Box 40)
    - Evie Robert's party; Villa Rosa (Box 40)
    - Evie Robert's christening, play, stable party (Box 40)
    - William Randolph Hearst's Christmas party in N.Y. (Box 40)